The American Society of Mammalogists

Number 4 inside front cover

Founded April 3, 1919

Incorporated April 29, 1920

C. Hart Merriam, President
E. W. Nelson; Wilfred H. Osgood, Vice-Presidents
H. H. Lane, Recording Secretary
Hartley H. T. Jackson, Corresponding Secretary
J. W. Gidley Treasurer
N. Hollister, Editor

Additional Directors

1919–1921 | 1920–1922
Gerrit S. Miller, Jr. | T. S. Palmer
Glover M. Allen | Rudolph M. Anderson
Witmer Stone | M. W. Lyon, Jr.
Joseph Grinnell | W. D. Matthew
John C. Merriam | Edward A. Preble

Standing Committees

Publications:
N. Hollister, Chairman. Gerrit S. Miller, Jr., Edward A. Preble, Hartley H. T. Jackson, J. W. Gidley.
Life Histories of Mammals:
Chas. C. Adams, Chairman. Rudolph M. Anderson, Vernon Bailey, Harold C. Bryant, Lee R. Dice, Hartley H. T. Jackson, T. S. Palmer, Ernest Thompson Seton, Walter P. Taylor, Herbert Lang.
Study of Game Mammals:
Charles Sheldon, Chairman. George Bird Grinnell.
Anatomy and Phylogeny:
W. K. Gregory, Chairman. John C. Merriam, H. H. Donaldson, Alexander Wetmore, Hermann von W. Schulte.
Bibliography:
T. S. Palmer, Chairman. Wilfred H. Osgood, Hartley H. T. Jackson.
Conservation
Wilfred H. Osgood, Chairman. E. W. Nelson, Jonathan Dwight.

The Journal of Mammalogy

Subscription rates, $3.50 per year; single numbers $1.00 each. Sent free to all members of the American Society of Mammalogists not in arrears for dues.

Manuscripts for publication, books and papers for notice and review, etc., should be sent to the Editor, N. Hollister, National Zoological Park, Washington, D. C.

Subscriptions, changes of addresses, requests for missing numbers, applications for advertising rates, etc., should be sent to the Corresponding Secretary, Dr. Hartley H. T. Jackson, Biological Survey, Washington, D.C.

List of Members of the American Society of Mammalogists

Volume 1 pages 201–212

Names of life members are marked with an asterisk.

Honorary Member

*Allen, Dr. J. A., American Museum of Natural History, New York City.

Members

*Abbott, Dr. William Louis, 400 South 15th Street, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
*Adams, Dr. Chas. C., New York State College of Forestry, Syracuse, New York.
*Ahrens, Dr. Theodor G., Landauerstrasse 4, Berlin Wilmersdorf, Germany.
*Ainsworth, Maj. Gen. F. C., The Concord, Washington, D. C.
*Akeley, Carl E., American Museum of Natural History, New York City.
*Albright, Horace M., Supt. Yellowstone National Park, Yellowstone Park, Wyoming.
*Alexander, Miss Annie M., Suisun, California.
*Alexander, E. Gordon, 1603 South Street, Lexington, Missouri.
*Allen, Dr. Arthur A., McGraw Hall, Ithaca, New York.
*Allen, Dr. Glover M., 234 Berkeley Street, Boston, Massachusetts.
*Anderson, Herbert A., R. F. D. 1, La Center, Washington.
*Anderson, Dr. Rudolph M., Biological Division, Geological Survey, Ottawa, Canada.
*Andrews, Roy C., American Museum of Natural History, New York City.
*Anthony, A. W., Ironside, Oregon.
*Anthony, H. E., American Museum of Natural History, New York City.
*Aschemeier, C. R., U. S. National Museum, Washington, D. C.
*Babcock, Dr. Harold L., Woodleigh Road, Dedham, Massachusetts.
*Badè, Dr. William Frederic, 2616 College Avenue, Berkeley, California.
*Bagg, Dr. Clinton L., 26 West 46th Street, New York City.
*Bailey, A. M., Juneau, Alaska.
*Bailey, Bernard, R. F. D. No. 1, Elk River, Minnesota.
*Bailey, Florence Merriam, 1834 Kalorama Road, N. W., Washington, D. C.
*Bailey, H. B., P. O. Box 112, Newport News, Virginia.
*Bailey, Harold H., 319 54th Street, Newport News, Virginia.
*Bailey, Vernon, 1834 Kalorama Road, N. W., Washington, D. C.
*Baird, Miss Katherine B., 815 Webster Street, N. W., Washington, D. C.
*Baker, A. B., National Zoological Park, Washington, D. C.
*Ball, Edward M., East Falls Church, Virginia.
*Bangs, Outram, Museum of Comparative Zoology, Cambridge, Massachusetts.
*Barbour, Dr. Thomas, Museum of Comparative Zoology, Cambridge, Massachusetts.
*Barnes, Claude T., 359 10th Avenue, Salt Lake City, Utah.
*Barrett, Charles H. M., 1339 Valley Place, S. E., Washington, D. C.
*Barrows, Prof. Walter B., P. O. Box 1047, East Lansing, Michigan.
*Bartlett, King, Locke’s Mills, Maine.
*Bascom, Kellogg F., Allegheny College, Meadville, Pennsylvania.
*Batchelder, Chas. F., 7 Kirkland Street, Cambridge, Massachusetts.
*Bateman, Robert E., Box 1251, Billings, Montana.
*Beach, William N., 30 East 42nd Street, New York City.
*Beck, Rollo H., R. R. A. 288, San Jose, California.
*Beebe, William, New York Zoological Park, New York City.
*Bell, Dr. W. B., 803 Rittenhouse Street, N. W., Washington, D. C.
*Bergtold, Dr. W. H., 1159 Race Street, Denver, Colorado.
*Biggs, O. S., San Jose, Illinois.
*Birdseye, Clarence, Yorktown Heights, New York.
*Bishop, Sherman C., Division of Zoology, New York State Museum, Albany, New York.
*Black, Prof. Davidson, Dept. of Anatomy, Peking Union Medical College, Peking, China.
*Blake, Prof. Irving H., Department of Biology, University of Maine, Orono, Maine.
*Boes, Raymond E., 675 South 6th East, Salt Lake City, Utah.
*Bolt, Benjamin F., 1421 Prospect Avenue, Kansas City, Missouri.
*Bowles, J. Hooper, The Woodstock, Tacoma, Washington.
*Bradshaw, F., Dept. of Agriculture, Regina, Alberta, Canada.
*Brannon, Peter A., Box 358, Montgomery, Alabama.
*Brimley, C. S., 1135 New Bern Avenue, Raleigh, North Carolina.
*Brimley, H. H., State Museum, Raleigh, North Carolina.
*Brode, Prof. H. S., Whitman College, Walla Walla, Washington.
*Brooks, A. B., 186 Lancaster Street, Albany, New York.
*Brooks, Allan, Okanagan Landing, British Columbia.
*Brooks, Fred E., French Creek, West Virginia.
*Brown, C. Emerson, Philadelphia Zoological Garden, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
*Brown, D. E., 87 Lenora Street, Seattle, Washington.
*Brown, E. J., 1609 S. Van Ness Avenue, Los Angeles, California.
*Brown, William L., National Museum, Washington, D. C.
*Brown, Wilmot W., c/o Benjamin Hood, Garces, Arizona.
*Bruette, William, 9 East 40th Street, New York City.
*Bruun, Charles A., Reliance Building, Kansas City, Missouri.
*Bryant, Dr. Harold C., Museum of Vertebrate Zoology, Berkeley, California.
*Bumstead, Col. Dale, 504 East Avenue, North, Oak Park, Illinois.
*Bunker, Charles D., Kansas University Museum, Lawrence, Kansas.
*Burgess, Thornton W., 61 Washington Road, Springfield, Massachusetts.
*Burnett, Wm. L., State Agricultural College, Fort Collins, Colorado.
*Burns, Frank L., Berwyn, Pennsylvania.
*Burrell, Harry, La Mascotte, Doncaster Avenue, Kensington, New South Wales, Australia.
*Burrell, Mrs. Harry, [Susan Emily], La Mascotte, Doncaster Avenue, Kensington, New South Wales, Australia.
*Burrill, Prof. Alfred C., U. S. Entomological Station, Forest Grove, Oregon.
*Butler, Amos W., 52 Downey Avenue, Irvington, Indianapolis, Indiana.
*Buwalda, Dr. John P., Peabody Museum, Yale University, New Haven, Connecticut.
*Cabrera, Ángel, Calle Claudio, Coello, 115, Madrid, Spain.
*Camp, Charles L., American Museum of Natural History, New York City.
*Campbell, Dr. Charles A. R., San Antonio Academy of Medicine, San Antonio, Texas.
*Campbell, Dr. J. A., 8 Edward Street, Toronto, Ontario.
*Cantwell, George G., 901 West Main Avenue, Puyallup, Washington.
*Carter, Franklin I., 1321 East 52nd Street, Chicago, Illinois.
*Case, Dr. E. C., University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, Michigan.
*Chambers, W. Lee, Eagle Rock, Los Angeles County, California.
*Chandler, W. L., Michigan Agricultural College, East Lansing, Michigan.
*Chapin, James P., American Museum of Natural History, New York City.
*Cheesman, William H., Biological Survey, U. S. Dept, of Agriculture, Washington, D. C.
*Church, Morton L., Box 1236, Charlotte, North Carolina.
*Clark, Dr. Bruce Lawrence, 202 Bacon Hall, University of California, Berkeley, California.
*Clark, Elton, 18 Post Office Square, Boston, Massachusetts.
*Clark, Wm. O., Framingham Centre, Massachusetts.
*Clark, Winslow, Shoreham, Addison County, Vermont.
*Clay, C. Irvin, P. O. Box 353, Eureka, California.
*Cockerell, Prof. T. D. A., 908 Tenth Street, Boulder, Colorado.
*Colburn, Albert E., 806 S. Broadway, Los Angeles, California.
*Conger, Prof. Allen C., Michigan Agricultural College, East Lansing, Michigan.
*Conover, Boardman, 6 Scott Street, Chicago, Illinois.
*Cooke, Miss May T., 1328 Twelfth Street, N. W., Washington, D. C.
*Coolidge, Dane, Dwight Way End, Berkeley, California.
*Cooper, J. P., Rome, Georgia.
*Cooper, Moses R., Kalispell, Montana.
*Copeland, Dr. Manton, Bowdoin College, Brunswick, Maine.
*Cornwall, James K., Edmonton, Alberta, Canada.
*Cory, Chas. B., Field Museum of Natural History, Chicago, Illinois.
*Couch, Leo K., Puyallup, Washington.
*Courtney, Wilbur, Pullman, Washington.
*Cram, William Everett, Hampton Falls, New Hampshire.
*Craven, J. W., 811 18th Street, Washington, D. C.
*Creaser, Charles W., 904 State Street, Alma, Michigan.
*Crick, Joe G., Jones-Hicks Ranch, Cuervo, New Mexico.
*Criddle, Norman, Treesbank, Manitoba, Canada.
*Criddle, Stuart, Treesbank, Manitoba, Canada.
*Dammerman, Karel Willem, Zoological Museum and Laboratory, Buitenzorg, Java
*Davison, Charles Stewart, 59 Wall Street, New York City, New York.
*Day, Dr. Lewis J., 3015 Wilson Avenue, Chicago, Illinois.
*Dearborn, Dr. Ned, Sacket Harbor, New York.
*Deuber, Carl G., State Agricultural College, Manhattan, Kansas.
*Dexter, Dr. John S., University of Saskatchewan, Saskatoon, Saskatchewan.
*Dice, Dr. Lee R., Museum of Zoology, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, Michigan.
*Dickerson, Mary C., American Museum of Natural History, New York City.
*Dickey, Donald R., San Rafael Heights, Pasadena, California.
*Dickinson, Charles W., 39 Mill Street, Smethport, Pennsylvania.
*Dille, Frederick M., Valentine, Nebraska.
*Dillon, W. Roy, Biological Survey, Washington, D. C.
*Dixon, Joseph S., Museum of Vertebrate Zoology, Berkeley, California.
*Donaldson, Dr. Henry H., The Wistar Institute, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
*Dwight, Dr. Jonathan, 43 West 70th Street, New York City.
*Edson, John M., Marietta Road, Bellingham, Washington.
*Eifrig, C. W. G., 504 Monroe Avenue, Oak Park, Illinois.
*Elliott, Mrs. Jane S., Biological Survey, U. S. Dept. Agriculture, Washington, D. C.
*Elrod, Prof. Morton J., Montana State University, Missoula, Montana.
*Evans, Victor J., Ninth Street and Grant Place, N. W., Washington, D. C.
*Evermann, Dr. Barton W., California Academy of Sciences, Golden Gate Park, San Francisco, California.
*Field, Dr. Geo. W., c/o Capt. Frederico Villar, C. A. “Jose Bonefacio,” Pernambuco, Brazil.
*Finley, William L., 651 East Madison Street, Portland, Oregon.
*Fisher, Dr. A. K., The Plymouth, 1236 11th Street, N. W., Washington, D.C.
*Fisher, Dr. G. Clyde, American Museum of Natural History, New York City.
*Fleischner, I. N., 207 Ash Street, Portland, Oregon.
*Fleming, J. H., 267 Rusholme Road, Toronto, Ontario.
*Freeman, Daniel, 711 Seventh Street, South, Fargo, North Dakota.
*Fribley, Earl F., Box 765, Phoenix, Arizona.
*Frick, Childs, Roslyn, Long Island, New York.
*Fuertes, Louis Agassiz, Cornell Heights, Ithaca, New York.
*Fuller, Arthur B., Boston Society of Natural History, 234 Berkeley Street, Boston, Massachusetts.
*Gabrielson, Ira N., 220 Post Office Building, Portland, Oregon.
*Gardner, Leon L., 3440 Walnut Street, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
*Garlough, F. E., 2208 Durant Avenue, Berkeley, California.
*Garretson, M. S., Clifton, New Jersey.
*Garrett, Cecil B. D., Box 512, Cranbrook, British Columbia.
*Gault, Benjamin T., 2313 Washington Boulevard, Chicago, Illinois.
*Gianini, Charles A., Poland, New York.
*Gidley, James W., U. S. National Museum, Washington, D. C.
*Gilchrist, D. A., Box 765, Phoenix, Arizona.
*Gillings, J. F., P. O. Box 1251, Billings, Montana.
*Gilman, M. French, Banning, California.
*Gilmore, Dr. Melvin R., State Historical Society, Bismarck, North Dakota.
*Gilpin, F. Robert, 5650 Hazel Avenue, Philadelphia, Pensylvania.
*Goethe, C. M., Capital National Bank Building, Sacramento, California.
*Goldman, E. A., Biological Survey, U. S. Dept. Agriculture, Washington, D. C.
*Goodwin, George G., American Museum of Natural History, New York City.
*Granger, Walter, American Museum of Natural History, New York City.
*Grant, Madison, 111 Broadway, New York City.
*Gregory, Dr. William K., American Museum of Natural History, New York City.
*Grinnell, Dr. George Bird, 238 East 15th Street, New York City.
*Grinnell, Dr. Joseph, Museum of Vertebrate Zoology, Berkeley, California.
*Gunthorp, Horace, University of Washington, Seattle, Washington.
*Gutsell, James S., Bureau of Fisheries, Washington, D. C.
*Gyldenstolpe, Count Nils, Naturhistoriska Riksmuseum, Stockholm, 50, Sweden.